Marcel Breuer Papers
Marcel Breuer Papers
- Project records
  - SAINT JOHN'S LIBRARY, Collegeville, MN (1960-1968). Marcel Breuer and Hamilton P. Smith, Architects. [Library]
    - Drawings, 282
      - Library Building (Oct 1964): Title sheet and reflected ceiling plan, site plan (Dwg. No. 1), upper floor (Dwg. No. 2), lower floor plan (Dwg. No. 3), mezzanine floor plan and construction plan (Dwg. No. 4), elevations and sections (Dwg. Nos. 5-6), presentation drawings (originals); 7 (Tube 1467)
    - Project files
      - Bid documents (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Change orders (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Contracts, owner-architect agreement (1960), owner-contractor agreement (1964) (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Associated architects (1964), Hanson-Michelson, Architects (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Awards (1968), AIA Library Building Awards Program (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Client (1959-1968), St. John's University (Box 100, Folder 6-10)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1960-1966), Gausman and Moore, construction engineers; Johnston-Sahlman Co., construction engineers; miscellaneous consultants (Box 101, Folder 11-13)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1964-1966), Cold Spring Electric Co. (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1964-1966), Gunnar I. Johnson Son, Inc. (Box 101, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Donors (1964), Dr. James Kritzeck (Box 101, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence: Field office (1965-1966), David Vachon (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: Grant (1965-1966), Title 45 grant materials (Housing Home Finance Agency; Dept. of Health, Education Welfare) (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1960-1965), Cold Spring Granite Co. (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1963), Contract Interiors, Inc. (Library Reading Table) (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1964), Century Lighting (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1960-1966), various suppliers and service providers (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Financial records (1957-1968), architectural invoices, certificates of payment, consultant invoices, Housing and Home Finance Agency periodic estimates for partial payment (Box 101, Folder 23-26)
      - Office records, St. John's University Building Committee meeting minutes, interoffice memoranda, miscellaneous notes, project records (Box 102, Folder 27-30)
      - Product literature (Box 102, Folder 31)
      - Program (Box 102, Folder 32)
      - Specifications, specifications for furnishings and equipment (Box 102, Folder 33)
      - Testing reports, Twin City Testing and Engineering Laboratory; Soil Exploration Co. (Box 102, Folder 34)
      - Transmittals (Box 102, Folder 35)
      - Library ecumenical offices
        - Correspondence: Client (1967), St. John's University (Box 102, Folder 1B)
        - Correspondence: Consultants (1967), Gausman and Moore, consulting engineers (Box 102, Folder 2B)
        - Correspondence: Contractor (1967), M.A. Mortenson Co., general contractor (Box 102, Folder 3B)
        - Financials (1957-1968), architectural and consultant invoices (Box 102, Folder 4B-5B)
        - Transmittals (Box 102, Folder 6B)
    - Published material
      - "A Pictorial Review of the New Library," The Off-Campus Record St. John's University (Winter 1965), magazine, pg. 16 (Box 102, Folder 39)
    - Photographs, 51
      - Elevation view from the north, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - Exterior wall detail, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - Progress photos of façade construction, construction, exterior view; black and white photographs; 19 (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - Progress photos of reading room and stacks, construction, interior view; black and white photographs; 7 (Box 102, Folder 37)
      - Tree column in main reading room, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 102, Folder 38)
      - Miscellaneous, "St. John's Library (SJL)", color slides; 21 (Box 207)
  - SAINT JOHN'S MONASTERY WING, Collegeville, MN (1953-1957). Marcel Breuer, Architect; Hamilton P. Smith, Associate. [Religious], (Alternate names: Breuer Monastic Wing; Monastery Gardens; St. John's Monastery); See also Saint John's Abbey and University Complex; Saint John's Church and Campanile.
    - Drawings, 243
      - Brothers' recreation room fireplace, presentation drawings (originals); pen and ink, applied film and opaque white on illustration board, 15 x 20 in.; 1 (Oversize 15)
      - Fathers' recreation room fireplace, presentation drawings (originals); pen and ink, applied film and opaque white on illustration board, 15 x 20 in.); 1 (Oversize 15)
      - Preliminary plan of monastery gardens, design development drawings (reproductions); 1 (Box 91, Folder 35)
      - SK drawings: Dwg. Nos. 70, 71 (3 copies), 72, 75, 77, 81, 84, 95B, 1 unnumbered, working drawings (originals); 11 (Box 91, Folder 36)
      - SK Set: Details and alternate layout schemes (Dwg. Nos. 1-94, working drawings (originals); incomplete; 72 (Tube 701)
      - Presentation set: Floor plans at three Levels (Sheet Nos.1-3), presentation drawings (originals); 3 (Tube 1135)
      - Furniture and cabinetry for Abbot's chapel (15-21 Feb 1956): Sheets C1-C3 and F7, working drawings (originals); 4 (Tube 1135)
      - Construction set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A1-A25), working drawings (originals); 25 (Tube 1135)
      - Construction set (28 May 1954- 20 Sep 1954): Structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S9); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4); plumbing (Dwg. No. P6); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. SM0, M1-M4), working drawings (originals); 19 (Tube 1136)
      - Sketch survey of existing building with colored differentiation of elevation zones, site surveys (originals); 1 (Tube 1123)
      - Counter proposal for monastery wing with multiple variations, design development drawings (reproductions); 3 (Tube 1123)
      - Construction details (Aug 1953- Feb 1955): Door schedule; preliminary wall sections and photo-mural mounting panels; furniture layouts for various monastery wing rooms; bench design, working drawings (originals); 25 (Tube 1123)
      - Landscaping (Dwg. Nos. L1-L2), working drawings (originals); 2 (Tube 1123)
      - Construction set (28 May 1954): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A1-A25), working drawings (reproductions); 25 (Tube 255)
      - Construction set (28 May 1954): Structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S9); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4); plumbing (Dwg. Nos. P2-P6); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M0-M4); heating and ventilating (Dwg. Nos. H1-H8); door location plans and schedules (Dwg. Nos. A-2 to A-6, A-16), working drawings (reproductions); 37 (Tube 254)
      - Construction set (28 May 1954) (print set): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A-4 to A-18, working drawings (reproductions); incomplete; 12 (Tube 253)
      - Third floor heating and ventilating plan, working drawings (reproductions); 1 (Tube 253)
    - Project files
      - Correspondence: Associated architects (1954-1956), Traynor and Hermanson, associated architects (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (1953-1957), St. John's Abbey personnel, including Fr. Meinberg, Fr. Eidenschink, Rt. Rev. Dworschak (Abbot), Frank Karmarcik (Box 90, Folder 3-6)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1955), Josef Albers (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1954), Cowin Co., Inc. (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Consultant (1954), Farkas and Barron, structural engineers (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Financial records, architectural invoices, certificates of payment, consultant invoices (Box 91, Folder 19-23)
      - Negatives for photomurals (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Office records, project memoranda, scale model, travel documents (Box 91, Folder 25-27)
      - Program (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - Specifications, general specifications (Box 91, Folder 29)
      - Transmittals, Covin Co., Inc. (Box 91, Folder 30-34)
    - Photographs, 16
      - Abbot's office [Slide 640], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Brothers' chapel [Slide 641], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Brothers' recreation room, finished project, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 91, Folder 37)
      - End wall [Slide 47], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Exterior view [Slide 10], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Exterior view [Slide 147], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Exterior view [Slide 156], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Group of monks with monastery building in background [Slide 155], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Monastic cell [Slide 636], finished project, interior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Partial elevation [Slide 602], finished project, exterior view; color slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Plan [Slide 9], drawings, plan; color slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - View at a distance with site context [Slide 151], finished project, exterior view; black and white slide; 1 (Box SL-6)
      - Miscellaneous, "St. John's Monastery (SJM)", color slides; 4 (Box 207)
  - SAINT JOHN'S RESIDENCE HALL I, Collegeville, MN (1957-1963). Marcel Breuer, Architect; Hamilton P. Smith, Associate. [Educational]
    (Alternate names: St. John's Residence Hall I; Saint John's University; Saint Thomas Aquinas Hall; St. Thomas Hall)
    See also Saint John's Abbey and University Complex; Saint John's Residence Hall II.
    - Drawings, 124
      - Construction set (4 Feb 1958): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A1-A19); structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S6), working drawings (originals); 25 (Tube 1337)
      - Construction set [4 Feb 1958]: Architectural (title sheet, Dwg. Nos. A2-A5, A7-A19); structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S6); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M1-M9); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4), working drawings (reproductions); annotated prints, some with sketches on back of sheets; 37 (Tube 262)
      - SK set (Feb 1958-Mar 1961): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. SKA2-SKA4, SKA6-SKA9); structural (Dwg. Nos. SKS1-SKS3); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. SKM1-SKM2); electrical (Dwg. Nos. SKEM-3RJ); Dwg. Nos. SKLU1, working drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 14 (Tube 262)
      - Construction set (4 Feb 1958): Mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M1-M9); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E4), working drawings (reproductions); 13 (Tube 261)
      - SK drawings and miscellaneous Details (Feb-Oct 1958): Dwg. Nos. SK1, SKA1-SKA12, SKS1-SKS3, Painting 1-2, Special Issue (P1), SKM1 and unnumbered, working drawings (originals); SKA set is incomplete; 19 (Tube 1338)
      - Furniture (Mar 1958-Mar 1959): Dwg. Nos. F1A, F2, F2A, F3A, F3a, F3b, working drawings (originals); 2 copies of F2; 8 (Tube 1338)
      - Dwg. No. A8, working drawings (reproductions); 1 (Tube 1338)
      - Site plan, design development drawings (reproductions); annotated print; 1 (Tube 1338)
      - Student residence hall: Photo murals (22 Jun 1959): Dwg. Nos. PM1-PM3, working drawings (originals and reproductions); 3 originals and 3 prints; 6 (Tube 1338)
    - Project files
      - Bid documents: Furnishings (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Change orders (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Associated architects (1957-1958), Traynor and Hermanson, Associated Architects (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Client (1957-1963), St. John's University (Box 92, Folder 4-5)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1957-1960), Gausman and Moore, construction engineers (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1957-1963), Wiesenfeld, Hayward and Leon, construction engineers (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1958-1959), Maurice Mandel, Inc. (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: Financing (1958-1959), Housing Home Finance Agency (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1958-1961), various suppliers and service providers (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence: Publicity (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence: Regulatory Agencies (1957-1960), Minnesota State Fire Marshall, Dept. of Health, Industrial Commission of Minnesota (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Financial records, architectural invoices, consultant invoices, periodic estimates and construction reports, insurance documents (Box 93, Folder 13-16)
      - Office records, Housing and Home Finance Agency office file; internal correspondence with field office (Val Michelson); project memoranda; travel documents (Box 93, Folder 17-20)
      - Specifications, furnishings proposals; furniture schedules; specifications for transformer installation (Box 93, Folder 21-23)
      - Testing reports, foundation investigation; Twin City Testing Laboratory concrete compression tests and cement reports (Box 93, Folder 24-25)
      - Transmittals (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Published material
      - "About 500 Persons Attended the Dedication... ," The Record (Aug 1959), newspaper clipping (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "Aquinas Hall to be Dedicated Aug. 9," The Record (24 Jul 1959), newspaper clipping (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "Brothers Fashion New Desks," The Record (27 Feb 1959), newspaper clipping (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "Johnnies Enjoy Plush Quarters," (25 Sep 1959), newspaper clipping (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "New Church, St. Thomas Hall Ahead of Schedule," The Record (10 Oct 1958), newspaper clipping (Box 93, Folder 28)
      - "Thomas Hall at Night," The Record (23 Oct 1959), newspaper clipping; photograph with caption (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, 39
      - Construction photos, finished project, exterior view; black and white photographs; prints and negatives; 19 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - Images for photomural, art work, detail; negatives; 10 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - View of two elevations, finished project, exterior view; black and white photograph; board mounted; 1 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous, "St. John's Residence Hall (SJR) I", color slides; 9 (Box 207)
  - SAINT JOHN'S RESIDENCE HALL II, Collegeville, MN (1961-1968). Marcel Breuer and Hamilton P. Smith, Architects. [Educational]
    (Alternate names: Saint Bernard Hall; Saint Boniface Hall; St. John's Residence Hall II; Saint John's University; Saint Patrick Hall)
    See also Saint John's Abbey and University Complex; Saint John's Residence Hall I.
    - Drawings, 230
      - Perspective rendering, presentation drawings (originals); graphite on illustration board, 12 x 28 in.; 1 (Map-case 115, Folder 3)
      - Detail for etched emblems in glass panels: Dwg. No. SK A-4, working drawings (reproductions); 1 (Box 106, Folder 35)
      - Furniture: Dwg. Nos. F2-F8A, working drawings (originals and reproductions); 10 (Box 106, Folder 35)
      - Construction set (15 Feb 1966): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A0-A21), working drawings (originals); 22 (Tube 1356)
      - Construction set (15 Feb 1966): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A0-A20); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E9, A9); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M1-M11, A9), working drawings (reproductions); marked "bid set"; annotated prints; 42 (Tube 259)
      - Construction set (15 Feb 1966): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A0-A20); structural (Dwg. Nos. S1-S7); electrical (Dwg. Nos. E1-E9); mechanical (Dwg. Nos. M1-M11), working drawings (reproductions); marked "revised bid set"; annotated prints; 47 (Tube 260)
      - Proposed student residence hall (Aug-Sep 1965): Dwg. Nos. H1-H3, presentation drawings (originals); H1 marked "void"; 4 (Tube 694)
      - Window panel and interior elevation of typical bedroom exterior wall (10 Dec 1965): Dwg. No. SK1, design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 694)
      - Miscellaneous design development drawings and sketches (Jul-Aug 1965), design development drawings (originals); 8 (Tube 694)
      - Schematic west elevation rendering, design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 694)
      - Site plan, design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 694)
      - Miscellaneous construction sheets (A0, A2-A5, A7-A9), design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; multiples of some sheets; 16 (Tube 1493)
      - Bid Sheet (Mar 1966), design development drawings (reproductions); 2 sheets; 2 (Tube 1493)
      - Student Dormitory Development Study (3 Sep 1965), design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 1 (Tube 1493)
      - Design development drawings, sketches and annotated prints (Oct 1965-Apr 1967), design development drawings (originals and reproductions); includes site plans, elevation and facade studies, pre-cast concrete panels, cafeteria plan, interior cabinets and furniture; 58 originals and 13 prints; 71 (Tube 1493-1494)
    - Project files
      - Bid documents (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Change orders (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Client (1961-1968), St. John's University (Box 105, Folder 3-4)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1965-1968), Edward Zekala, architectural specifications; Gausman and Moore, consulting engineers; Johnston-Sahlman Co., consulting engineers; various consultants (Box 105, Folder 5-8)
      - Correspondence: Contractors (1966-1968), M.A. Mortenson Co., general contractor; Knapp Plumbing Heating, Inc.; Cold Spring Electric Co. (Box 105, Folder 9-11)
      - Correspondence: Field office (1966-1967), Norman Dorf, David Vachon, Noel Jones (Field Engineer) (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: Grant (1966), Dept. of Housing Urban Development application materials, HHFA Periodic Inspection Reports (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence: Manufacturers (1965-1967), various suppliers and service providers; Cold Spring Granite Co. (Box 105, Folder 14-15)
      - Correspondence: Regulatory agencies (1966), Minnesota fire marshall (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Financial records (1957-1968), architectural invoices; building costs; certificates of payment; consultant invoices; insurance certificate (Box 106, Folder 17-23)
      - Office records, field office expenses, memoranda (Box 106, Folder 24-25)
      - Program, program-area analysis (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - Punch lists (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Site certificate, includes site survey (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - Specifications, preliminary specification for mechanical utilities work, furnishing specifications (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - Testing reports, Soil Exploration Co. (Box 106, Folder 30)
      - Transmittals (Box 106, Folder 31-32)
    - Photographs, 18
      - Façade construction photos, construction, exterior view; black and white photographs; 14 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Stair railing installation, construction, interior view; black and white photograph; 1 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Views of facades and close-ups, finished project, exterior view; black and white photographs; 3 (Box 106, Folder 34)
  - SAINT JOHN'S SCIENCE BUILDING, Collegeville, MN (1962-1968). Marcel Breuer and Hamilton P. Smith, Architects. [Educational]
    (Alternate names: Peter Engel Science Center; Saint John's University; Science Center)
    - Drawings, 377
      - Construction set (1 Mar 1965): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A0-A27), working drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 28 (Tube 257)
      - Construction set (1 Mar 1965): Architectural (Dwg. Nos. A24-A27), working drawings (reproductions); prints of revised sheets; 4 (Tube 257)
      - Occupancy and egress set (13 Nov 1964), working drawings (reproductions); 5 (Tube 257)
      - Construction set (1 Mar 1965): Architectural (A0-A21, A23-A27), working drawings (originals); 27 (Tube 1334)
      - Test boring and survey data (6 Jul 1964), site surveys (originals); 1 (Tube 1334)
      - SK drawing set (Sep 1964-Jan 1965): SK1-SK100, design development drawings (originals); incomplete; 40 (Tube 1335)
      - SK-D (13 Jan 1964), design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 1335)
      - SK-B-1, design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 1335)
      - SK architectural set (Aug 1965-Oct 1965): SK-A-1 to SK-A-19 and unnumbered, design development drawings (originals); 28 (Tube 1335)
      - Architect's report (Aug 1964): Sheets 1-9, presentation drawings (reproductions); 1 set negative photostats, 1 set positive photostats; 18 (Tube 1336)
      - Presentation set (Aug 1964): Site plan, floor plans, elevations, sections, auditorium sections (Sheet Nos. 1-8), presentation drawings (originals and reproductions); 1 complete set and 2 duplicate sets without Sheet No. 8; 22 (Tube 1336)
      - Design development sketches and drawings, design development drawings (originals); includes sketch renderings, elevation studies, plan studies, auditorium plans and interior elevations, building sections; 57 (Tube 1462)
      - Preliminary HVAC Plans (29 Jun 1964) (Gausman and Moore): Dwg. No. SK-—1 to SK-—4, consultant drawings (reproductions); 4 (Tube 1463)
      - Design development sketches and drawings, design development drawings (originals); includes perspective renderings, window details, plan studies, lab plans, early sketches (before 13 Apr 1964); 28 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary scheme (9 Apr 1964), design development drawings (originals and reproductions); 1 original and 4 annotated prints; 5 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary scheme (13 Apr 1964), design development drawings (originals and reproductions); 1 original and 1 annotated print; 2 (Tube 1463)
      - Space use diagram (11 May 1961), design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 1463)
      - Comparative schemes (11 May 1964), design development drawings (originals and reproductions); 1 original and 1 print; 2 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964): Floor plans and elevations (Dwg. Nos. 2-7), design development drawings (originals); 6 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964, date stamped 11 May 1964): Dwg. Nos. 2-6, design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 5 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964, date stamped 6 May-27 May 1964): Dwg. Nos. 1-7, design development drawings (reproductions); marked as "office set"; annotated prints; 8 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964, date stamped 27 May 1964): Dwg. Nos. 2-7, design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 6 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964, date stamped 5 Aug 1964): Dwg. Nos. 3, 6, design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 2 (Tube 1463)
      - Preliminary plans (11 May 1964, date stamped 21 Aug 1964): Dwg. Nos. 2-5, design development drawings (reproductions); annotated prints; 4 (Tube 1463)
      - Space Allocation Diagram (Mar 1964), design development drawings (originals); 1 (Tube 1463)
      - Rendering, design development drawings (reproductions); photostats, multiple copies; 3 (Tube 1463)
      - Design development and preliminary working drawings:, design development drawings (originals); includes site work, elevation studies, plan studies, window details, structural studies, auditorium plans and interior elevations, concrete details; 66 (Tube 1464)
    - Project files
      - Bid documents (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Client (1964-1967), St. John's University (Box 103, Folder 2-3)
      - Correspondence: Consultants (1964-1967), Gausman and Moore, Inc., consulting engineers; Goodfriend-Ostergaard Associates, consulting acoustical engineers; Johnston-Sahlman, consulting engineers; Edward Zekala, architectural specifications (Box 103, Folder 4-8)
      - Correspondence: Contractor (1965-1968), Gunnar I. Johnson Sons, Inc. (Box 103, Folder 9-11)
      - Correspondence: Field office (1965-1967), David Vachon (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence: Grant (1962-1968), Title 45 application materials (Box 104, Folder 13)